{
    "subject": "resource/Auja_al-Hafir",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Auja al-Hafir, also Auja, was an ancient road junction close to water wells  in the western Negev and eastern Sinai. It was  the traditional grazing land of the 'Azazme tribe. The border crossing between Egypt and Ottoman/British Palestine, about 60 km (37 mi) south of Gaza, was situated there. Today it is the site of Nitzana and the Ktzi'ot military base in  the Southern District of Israel.",
    "human_readable": "Auja al-Hafir was an ancient road junction close to water wells in the western Negev and eastern Sinai.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8992475271224976,
            "question": "What evidence suggests that Auja al-Hafir was an important road junction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8699392080307007,
            "question": "What was the significance of water wells at Auja al-Hafir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8267656564712524,
            "question": "Where was Auja al-Hafir located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7491775155067444,
            "question": "Which regions encompassed Auja al-Hafir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.685947835445404,
            "question": "What type of historical site is Auja al-Hafir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726130247116089,
            "question": "Can you describe the historical context of Auja al-Hafir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6436374187469482,
            "question": "Why might Auja al-Hafir have been a significant location in ancient times?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059942245483398,
            "question": "What can we learn about ancient trade routes from Auja al-Hafir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5632496476173401,
            "question": "What characterized Auja al-Hafir geographically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5417976975440979,
            "question": "How might the location of Auja al-Hafir have influenced its development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Auja al-Hafir was an ancient road junction close to water wells in the western Negev and eastern Sinai.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2582_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What characterized Auja al-Hafir geographically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2582_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we learn about ancient trade routes from Auja al-Hafir?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2582_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might Auja al-Hafir have been a significant location in ancient times?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2582_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2582_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis query is supported by the information provided in the documents, which state that \"Auja al-Hafir, also Auja, was an ancient road junction close to water wells in the western Negev and eastern Sinai.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}